{
    "subject": "Laurence_Harvey",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Margaret_Leighton",
    "human_readable": "Laurence Harvey is married to Margaret Leighton.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9884039163589478,
            "question": "Is Margaret Leighton married to Laurence Harvey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9706870913505554,
            "question": "What is known about the marriage of Laurence Harvey and Margaret Leighton?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9451873898506165,
            "question": "Were Laurence Harvey and Margaret Leighton a couple?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9208521842956543,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the relationship between Laurence Harvey and Margaret Leighton?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8968921303749084,
            "question": "Who are Laurence Harvey and Margaret Leighton?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8951839804649353,
            "question": "Is there a famous couple named Laurence Harvey and Margaret Leighton?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8935500979423523,
            "question": "Who is Laurence Harvey married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8895605206489563,
            "question": "Who was married to Margaret Leighton?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8224030137062073,
            "question": "What is the connection between Laurence Harvey and Margaret Leighton?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6205617785453796,
            "question": "What is the name of Laurence Harvey's wife?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Laurence Harvey is married to Margaret Leighton.",
            "html": "yago_28674_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the connection between Laurence Harvey and Margaret Leighton?",
            "html": "yago_28674_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was married to Margaret Leighton?",
            "html": "yago_28674_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Laurence Harvey married to?",
            "html": "yago_28674_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28674_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28674_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28674_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28674_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28674_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28674_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28674_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28674_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28674_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28674_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents support this triple, as there are multiple mentions of Laurence Harvey and Margaret Leighton being a couple. For example, in one document, it says \"Margaret Leighton with husband and fellow actor Laurence Harvey\", and in another document, it says \"Laurence Harvey and Margaret Leighton arrived back in London yesterday\" and also \"Laurence Harvey and Margaret Leighton are divorced after a marriage of 4 years\". This suggests that they were indeed married."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references indicating that Laurence Harvey was indeed married to Margaret Leighton. Documents like `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_28674/re-ranker-msmarco/61.txt` and `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_28674/re-ranker-msmarco/26.txt` explicitly state that Laurence Harvey and Margaret Leighton were divorced after a marriage of 4 years, which implicitly confirms their past marital relationship."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}